In this section, we're going to explore the
Nesta seo, vamos explorar os fundamentos do
fundamentals of unit testing. So you're going to learn about characteristics
teste de unidade. Ento voc aprender sobre
of good unit tests. What to test and what not to test,
caractersticas de bons testes unitrios. O que testar e o que no testar,
this is one of the common questions I get from a lot of my students,
essa  uma das perguntas mais comuns que recebo de muitos dos meus alunos, eles
they say, "Mosh, I don't know what to test!" So in this section, I'm going to give you some
dizem: "Mosh, no sei o que testar! "Ento, nesta seo, vou dar algumas
guidelines that help you get started. You're also going to learn about
orientaes que ajudaro voc a comear. Voc tambm aprender sobre como nomear
naming and organizing your tests, along with some basic
e organizar seus testes, alm de algumas tcnicas bsicas para escrever testes
techniques for writing clean and maintainable tests. And finally you're
limpos e de fcil manuteno. E finalmente voc aprender
going to learn how to write reliable tests that don't lie.
a escrever testes confiveis que no mentem.
So, when they pass, you know that your production code is working,
Assim, quando eles passam, voc sabe que seu cdigo de produo est funcionando e,
and when they fail, you know that there is something wrong in the production code.
quando eles falham, voc sabe que h algo errado no cdigo de produo.
So now, let's get started!
Ento agora vamos comear!